

MD MAHAFUZUR RAHAMAN PYTHON DJANGO

Contact

DEVELOPER



North Lamchari, Barisal Sadar, Barisal



+8801317975131



mafuzur22.github.io/getaintro



mfrahaman22@gmail.com



Project Management

•••••

Python & Django

•••••

Linux System Admin

•••••

Web Development

•••••



About Me

Respectful self-motivator gifted at finding reliable solutions for software issues. Experienced in Django and Python and offering skills in Web-App Development and Management. Fluent in English and accustomed to working with cross- cultural, global teams.

Education

Secondary School Certificate

2016-2020 GPA: 4.28

Bukhainagar High School

Diploma In Computer Enginnering

2020-2024 CGPA: 3.42

Infra Polytechnic Institute

Work Experience

Django Projects

Self-Initiated Projects

October 2022 - November 2022

- Designed and developed web applications using Django, Python, and HTML/CSS.
- Created a blog application with user authentication, CRUD operations, and responsive design.
- · Deployed applications on platforms like Linode

Machine Learning Projects

Self-Initiated Projects

July 2023 - Present

- Implemented a predictive model for forecasting using historical data and time series analysis.
- Developed Feed Forward Neural Net and used it for chatBot Development.

Linux From Scratch (LFS)

Self-Initiated Projects

August 2023 - Present

- Built a custom Linux operating system from scratch using the Linux From Scratch (LFS) project.
- Gained hands-on experience with system programming, compilation, and configuration of Linux kernel and essential system components.